import 'package:quizapp/models/question.dart';

const List<Question> questions = [
  Question(
    question: '1. What does the keyword "var" in JavaScript declare?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    options: [
      'a) A variable',
      'b) A constant',
      'c) A function',
      'd) A class',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question:
        '2. Which programming language is known as the backbone of web development?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
    options: [
      'a) Python',
      'b) C++',
      'c) JavaScript',
      'd) Java',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '3. What is the main purpose of the "git" command?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    options: [
      'a) Compile code',
      'b) Version control',
      'c) Debug code',
      'd) Execute scripts',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '4. In Python, what does the "def" keyword define?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
    options: [
      'a) A loop',
      'b) A class',
      'c) A function',
      'd) A module',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '5. What does CSS stand for?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
    options: [
      'a) Computer Style Sheets',
      'b) Creative Style Sheets',
      'c) Cascading Simple Sheets',
      'd) Cascading Style Sheets',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question:
        '6. Which language is primarily used for Android app development?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    options: [
      'a) Swift',
      'b) Java',
      'c) Ruby',
      'd) C#',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '7. What is the main use of SQL?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    options: [
      'a) Managing databases',
      'b) Designing websites',
      'c) Writing applications',
      'd) Creating graphics',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '8. Which of the following is a Python web framework?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
    options: [
      'a) Angular',
      'b) React',
      'c) Django',
      'd) Laravel',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '9. What is the main purpose of HTML?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    options: [
      'a) Styling web pages',
      'b) Structuring web content',
      'c) Programming logic',
      'd) Managing databases',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '10. In which language is TensorFlow written?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    options: [
      'a) Python',
      'b) Java',
      'c) C++',
      'd) JavaScript',
    ],
  ),
];
